Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.fourtee Mss.B.B61.inventory14
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (W-Z)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory14
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents W
  - W., I. H. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 20
    - Treasurer's Report
  - Waaland, H., 1935 Aug. 9; 1p (Box 93)
  - Wadelton, H. C. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 27
  - Wagenknecht, A. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1933 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 3; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1933, 1p
  - Wagenseih, F. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1925 May 18; 1p
  - Wagner (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 9
  - Wagner, A. H. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 10; 4p
  - Wagner, Charles (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 June 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 July 23
    - To Boas, 1914 July 23
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 1p
  - Wagner, Günter (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1928 July 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 July 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 12; 7p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 17; 8p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 6; 5p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 30; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 5p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 30; 3p
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), 1937 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 23; 2p
  - Wagner, Herman (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1885 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1887 July 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 18; 4p
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 16; 6p
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 June 9
  - Wagner, Leopold (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 10; 1p
  - Wagner, M. L. (Box 93)
    - 1913 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 14; 7p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 22; 2p
    - From Junge & Sohn, 1920 Feb. 17; 1p
  - Wagner, Robert F. Jr. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 22; 1p
  - Wailny, F. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1908 June 1
  - Waite, Mary L. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 3p
  - Waites, Alfred (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1893 Jan. 4; 2p
  - Wake, C. Staniland (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1894 June 20
    - To Boas, 1894 July 8
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 6
      Scope and Contents note
      See: Schulte, F.J.
  - Wakeman, F. W. (Box 93)
    - To Mrs. F.R. Hoesington, 1912 June 24
  - Wakeman, Seth (Box 93)
    - See Boas, F. (open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies.), 1938 Jan.
  - Walcott, Charles D. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 31; 3p
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 7; 6p
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 7; 6p
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1908 May 4
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 May 4; 4p
    - From Boas, 1909 July 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1909 July 10; 17 p
    - From Boas, 1909 July 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1909 July 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 20
    - See Boas, F. (to Walcott, C. D.), 1909 July 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 3; 5p
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 8; 7p
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 23; 4p
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5
    - From Boas, 1910 May 20
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 29
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 27
    - From Boas, 1911 May 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 May 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 30; 10p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 2; 11p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 June 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Sep. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1908 May 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 May 5
    - To Boas, 1909 May 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 8
    - See Boas, F. (to Walcott, C. D.), 1909 July 10
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 18
    - See Boas, F. (to Walcott, C. D.), 1909 July 10
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1910 May 4
    - To Boas, 1910 May 23
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1911 May 15
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 22; 1p
    - From G.E. Chamberlain, 1918 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Dorsey, George A., 1909 July 25
    - To Frachtenberg, 1913 Feb. 13
    - To Frachtenberg, 1917 Oct. 30
    - To Frachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 7
    - From Frachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 2
    - To Young, A. A., 1917 Nov. 24
    - From McGee, W. J., 1910 Jan. 26
    - From McGee, W. J., 1910 Apr. 20
    - From McGee, W. J., 1910 Apr. 28
    - From Young, A.A., 1917 Mov. 23
    - The Walcott Affair
      See
    - Boas, F. (to Archaeological Institute of America - President and Council), 1909 Dec. 24
    - Boas, F. (to Kelsey, F.W.), 1910 Dec. 16
    - Boas, F. (open letter), 1911 Nov. 13
    - Knapp, Charles (to Spencer,), 1911 Jan. 13
    - Spencer, N.S., 1911 Jan. 16
    - Spencer, N.S., 1911 Jan. 31
    - Spencer, N.S. (to Kelsey, F.), 1911 Feb. 16
    - Spencer, N.S. (to Kelsey, F.), 1911 Feb. 20
    - Spencer, N.S. (to Kelsey, F.), 1911 Feb. 24
    - Spencer, N.S. (to Kelsey, F.), 1911 Feb. 27
    - Kelsey, F.W. (to Spencer, N.), 1911 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 2
    - Spencer, N.S., 1911 Feb. 17
    - (to Boas, F.), 1911 Mar. 4
    - (to Boas, F.), 1911 Mar. 14
    - (to Boas, F.), 1911 Mar. 28
    - (to Boas, F.), 1911 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 28
    - From Wierum, Otto C., Jr., 1911 June 10
    - Boas, F. (to Hewett, E.L.), 1911 Nov. 13
  - Walcott, W. D. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1910 June 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 6
  - Waldenfels, von (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 10; 4p
  - Waldenstein(sic)Waldenfels (cont'd) Freiherr von (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 17; 1p
  - Waldman, Morris D. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 July 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Aug. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1938 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 June 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 26; 1p
    - Enc. Adler, Cyrus (to Waldman, M.), 1938 July 18
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Adler, Cyrus, 1938 July 18
    - Enc. with Waldman, M.D., 1938 July 26
  - Waldo, Alice (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Waldstein, A. S. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 27; 1p
    - From The Macmillan Co., 1930 June 26
  - Walett (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1902 June 5
  - Walfram (Box 93)
    - See Gruepe, 1909 Apr. 14
  - Walker, A. L. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 18
  - Walker, Edward B. (Box 93)
    - To Keppel, F. P., 1906 Aug. 20
  - Walker, E. C. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 11; 1p
  - Walker, Helen M. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 2p
  - Walker, J. C. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
  - Walker, L. C. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1890 June 29
  - Walker, Madeleine (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 23; 1p
  - Walker, S. C. (Box 93)
    - See Pegram, G.B. (to Cabanellas), 1937 Feb. 11
  - Walker, S. H. (Box 93)
    - To Fackenthal, F. D., 1933 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Wallace (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 29
  - Wallace, Amy (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 31
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1907 Apr. 8
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 23; 1p
  - Wallace, S.C. (Box 93)
    - See Pegram, G.B. (to Cabanellas), 1937 Feb. 11
  - Wallace, William (Box 93)
    clerk, American Museum of Natural History
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 12
  - Wallach, Sidney (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 8; 1p
    - Enc. Statement about racial descent of the Jews, 1935 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 June 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 24; 4p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 29; 1p
    - Enc: Adler, C. Address at Dropsie College - Extract, 1934 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1935 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Sep. 26; 1p
    - From Leary, D. B.
    - See Leary, D.B. Found at end of, 1935 Oct.
  - Wallerstein, Dr. Leo (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 18; 1p
      Enc. List
    - Stein, F.M. (to Wallerstein, L.), 1933 Oct. 17
    - Wallerstein, L. (to Dreyfus, C.), 1933 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Wallerstein Co. to Benedict, R.F., 1938 June 17; 1p
    - To Dreyfus, C., 1938 Oct. 18; 1p
    - Enc. with Wallerstein, Leo, 1933 Oct. 18
    - From Stein, F.M., 1933 Oct. 17
    - Enc. with Wallerstein, Leo, 1933 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1938 July 26; 1p
    - From Wallerstein Co.
  - Walling, Elizabeth B. (Box 93)
    - See Boas, F. (to Villard, O.G.), 1939 May 23
      See Boas, F. (open letter)
      - Found at end of Dec. 1939
  - Walling, W. E. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 15
  - Wallis, Ruth Sawtell (Box 93)
    See Sawtell, R. O.
  - Wallis, Wilson D. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1928 July 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 July 11
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1928 July 26; 1p
    - See Boas, F., 1931 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p
  - Wallis, Mrs. Wilson (Box 93)
  - Walsh, F. P. (Box 93)
    - See McConnell, F. J., 1939 Jan. 25
  - Walsh, J. Raymond (Box 93)
    - See Boas, F. (to Villard, O.G.), 1939 May 23
    - Found at end of Dec. 1939
  - Walsh, Joseph (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
  - Walsh, T. J. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 25; 1p
  - Walt, W. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 31; 2p
      Enc:
  - Walter, Max (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 26; 2p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1920, 4p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Reinhardt, Walter, 1922 Dec.; 2p
    - Attached to letter, dated Dec. 22 1922
    - to Boas, F. from Reinhardt, Walter
  - Walther, Johannes (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To the American members of the Imperial Leopoldina German Academy, 1927 Mar.
    - Found at end of Mar. 1927
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 11; 1p
  - Walton, B. W. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1927 July 11; 4p
  - Walton, E. L. (Box 93)
    - See Boas, F., 1931 Nov. 22
    - To Devine, E. T., 1905 Mar. 29
  - Walton, G. M. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
  - Walton, Lester A. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1916 May 17
    - To Boas, 1916 May 15; 4p
  - Walz, John A. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 20; 2p
      - Enc:, 1920 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 22; 1p
    - To Rektor of Universitat Freiburg in Raden, 1920 Oct. 8; 3p
  - Wankel, H. (Box 94)
    Native American Images note
    Photomechanical print of bone
    - To Boas, 1893 Apr. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1893 June 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 5; 2p
  - Wanner, Theodor G. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 15; 1p
  - Warburg, A. (Box 94)
    - Photocopies from The Warburg Institute, London, 1895 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 14; 3p
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 June 4; 1p
    - Photocopies from The Warburg Institute, London, 1927 Mar. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 13; 6p
    - Photocopies from The Warburg Institute, London, 1896 Jul. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 21; 1p
  - Warburg, E.M.M. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 16
  - Warburg, Felix M. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1902 June 2
    - From Boas, 1908 May 29
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 8; 4p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 17; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 26; 3p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 5; 3p
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 28; 3p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 July 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 July 15; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1905, 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1914 May 1
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Adler, C., 1924 Oct. 3
    - From May, 1934 May 3
    - From Osborn, H. F., 1913 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 12
    - To Osborn, H. F., 1913 Dec. 16
    - To Sherwood, G. H., 1925 Nov. 5; 1p
    - From Sherwood, G. H., 1925 Nov. 7
    - From Zollschan, T., 1933 Dec.
  - Warburg, Ingrid (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 4; 1p
  - Warburg, James (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 19; 1p
  - Warburg, Max (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 7p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 June 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 July 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1942 Sep. 14; 3p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1942 July 10; 1p
      Enc: Rosenblum, David
    - To Warburg, Max, 1942 July 9
  - Warburg, Max M. (cont'd) (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1942 Sep. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 30; 1p